oneonlinegames.com 2017-12-23

# Privacy Policy and Copyrights Free Games Download

**Your Privacy at OneOnlineGames.com**

We collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, we collect and store certain information automatically. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website.

What We Collect and Store Automatically  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website.  
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site.  
The date and time you access our site.  
The pages you visit.  
If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.  
We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

If You Send Us E-mail You may choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations.

**Report Copyright Infringement**

All games and trademarks on this site are copyright their respective owners. 

If you feel a game hosted on OneOnlineGames.com has been used in error or without proper permission, please 

and it will be removed. 

**Cookies**  
To save you logging in everytime you visit OneOnlineGames.com, we place a little text file called a "cookie" on your hard drive. It sits in your web browser directory.

A cookie lets us store your profile information on your computer and let's our web site retrieve it when you visit our site. No other web site can use or view the cookie set by OneOnlineGamesl.com.

Cookies help us create a speedy web experience by remembering your address and email information, so you don't have to re-type it when making multiple purchases. They also enable you to recall previous purchases.

Cookies do not store credit card information and we do not use them to track your movements through our site.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our website has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

**Restriction of Liability**

OneOnlineGames.com makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.

Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by OneOnlineGames.com

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

"WEBSITE/PUBLISHER NAME" uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Mollom**

Some forms(comments, contact us, etc) are protected by Mollom (3rd party), please see their [Mollom privacy policy](http://mollom.com/web-service-privacy-policy)
